[Music]
M Ki you're getting
fat
me getting fat how can you say that I'm
not getting fat though I said you're
getting fat see you better stop that I
said I'm not getting
fat me that is tall and plumpy he so I'm
getting fat I don't like that though
better stop it you better mind your own
business he mana
come aunti good afternoon good afternoon
emuel look at me am I getting
[Music]
fat mhm no you are not getting fat you
already fat come on go to your house
I'm not getting fat I'm only adding
flesh yes fat flesh look at this little
girl do you know what it means to be fat
see auntie I know five fat people in
this compound and you're three of them
me you better start
[Laughter]
drinking